Effective Date: March 2, 2023

1\. Introduction.

We at Next Admit LLC know you care about how your personally identifiable information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy (the "Policy"). By using or accessing the Services in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the following ways. Any capitalized terms that are not defined in this Policy are defined in our Terms of Service ("Terms").

**Acceptance of This Privacy Policy.** By using our Services (whether or not You register or create any kind of account with us), you accept the terms set forth in this Policy as well as in the Terms. Anyone that does not agree to the terms of this Policy and the Terms, should not use our Services. You agree that your only recourse if you do not agree to the terms of this Policy and the Terms shall be to discontinue using our Services. By using our Services, you consent to having your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States or any other country in which we may have offices, employees, independent contractors or wherever our servers may be located.

**Consent.** By using our Services you consent to our Policy, as well as the limitation of liability, arbitration, refund policy and all the other Terms that form the Agreement.

2\. Information We May Collect.

1. **Voluntarily disclosed information.** Voluntarily disclosed information. You agree that we may collect the following information about you: Name, contact information, including email address, phone number, age, gender, IP (Internet Protocol) address, information supplied during the processing of registering with us, data usage trends, data showing the effectiveness of promotional campaigns, browser information, demographic information, browsing preferences, browsing data, the type of device being used, website usage information, information regarding any URLs used with the Services, data regarding use of our Services, other information relevant to surveys and/or offers, and any other information we are legally allowed to collect.
    
    When you use the Services, you will have the opportunity to provide us with some information directly. For example, some functions of the Services require you to register for an account, where we may ask you for your name, email address and phone number. As another example, we may also collect other information you directly give us as you build your profile through the Services, including but not limited to your, demographic information, GPA, test scores, race/ethnicity, academic awards and any other information that appears on a college application, including but not limited to, the common application, the coalition application, individual school applications, and supplemental materials ("College Application").
    
    If you opt to use our College Application review as part of our Services, users may redact or omit any piece of Information they do not wish to share with us or for us to collect. IN ANY EVENT, ALL USERS ARE REQUIRED TO REDACT OR OMIT THEIR SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER IN ORDER TO USE OUR SERVICES.
    
2. **Automatically collected information.** Whenever you interact with our Services, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser or device, which may include your IP address, geolocation data, device identification, "cookie" information, the type of browser and/or device you're using to access our Services, and the page or feature you requested. "Cookies" are identifiers we transfer to your browser or device that allow us to recognize your browser or device and tell us how and when pages and features in our Services are visited and by how many people. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser or device to prevent or limit your device's acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of some of our features.
    
    We may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. This confirmation helps us make our communications with you more interesting and improve our Services.
    
    We may use this data to customize content for you that we think you might like, based on your usage patterns. We may also use it to improve the Services – for example, this data can tell us how often users use a particular feature of the Services, and we can use that knowledge to make the Services interesting to as many users as possible.
    
3. **Heat Map and Tracking Software.** We may use various types of tracking software ("Tracking Software") to track mouse movement, scrolling, time spent on a page/screen, pages/screens visited, and clicks in order to better understand our users' needs and to optimize the use of our Services. The most common form of Tracking Software is referred to as a "heat map" and the forms of heat maps include scroll maps, click maps, and movement maps. Heat maps are graphical representations of data where values are depicted by color. Users hereby specifically agree to our use of Tracking Software and heat maps.
    
    Our Tracking Software may capture screen shots of users' mouse movements, scrolling, and clicking habits which helps us understand what users want, care about, and do when using our Services by visually representing their clicks, taps and scrolling behavior. Some of the reasons why we use heat map software are as follows: to see if Users are reaching important content or failing to see it, to find and use a page's main links, buttons, opt-ins, and calls to action ("CTAs"), to see if users are getting distracted by non-clickable elements, and to compare usage against mobile, tablet and desktop devices.
    
    We use Tracking Software to help us better understand our users' experience (e.g. how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click, what Users do and don't like, etc.) and this enables us to build and maintain our Services with user feedback. This Traffic Software uses cookies and other technologies to collect data on our users' behavior and their devices. This includes a device's IP address (processed during your website visit and stored in a de-identified form), device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), and the preferred language used to display our content. This Tracking Software stores this information on our behalf.
    
4. **Website and Application Analytics.** We use multiple web analytics tools provided by service partners, including but not limited to, Google Analytics to collect information about how you interact with our website, including what pages you visit, what site you visited prior to visiting our website, how much time you spend on each page, what operating system and web browser you use and network and IP information. Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our website and Services. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. We use the information provided by these tools to improve our Services. These tools place persistent cookies in Your browser to identify You as a unique user the next time you visit our Website. Each cookie cannot be used by anyone other than the service provider (example: Google for Google Analytics). The information collected from the cookie may be transmitted to and stored by these service partners on servers in a country other than the country in which you reside. Though information collected does not include personal data such as name, address, billing information, etc., the information collected is used and shared by these service providers in accordance with their individual privacy policies. You can control the technologies we use by utilizing settings in your browser or third-party tools. You can opt-out of making Your activity available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy.
    
5. **Targeted Advertisements.** Targeted ads or interest-based offers may be presented to you based on your activities on our website. These offers will display as varying product banners presented to you while browsing. We may also partner with third parties to manage our advertising on our webpages. Our third party partners may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about such activities in order to provide you with advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests, and to measure advertising effectiveness. If you are in the US or Canada and wish to opt out of interest-based advertising visit http://preferences- mgr.truste.com If You are located in the European Union visit www.Youronlinechoices.eu. Please note You will continue to receive generic ads.

3\. What We Do With the Information We Gather.

You agree that Next Admit may use the information we gather as follows: In order to process your purchase of Services, we must share certain personal information every time a user signs up for our Services. Such information may include the user's e-mail address, physical address, phone number, and credit card information. Our representatives may use your telephone number or e-mail address to notify you of the status of your purchase as necessary and appropriate. We may share user information with vendors, business clients, and other third-party providers who are performing services for us. We may also use your information for internal record keeping and data analysis. For our statistical purposes, we gather details of user visits to our website and the information that users access, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, browser usage, page visits, weblogs, and other communication data. When you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. We also use your information to ensure that content and the functionality of our services and software are presented in the most effective manner for computer or mobile devices.

From time to time, personal financial information (including credit card information) may be transmitted to facilitate transactions with Next Admit. We will not share such personal financial information with third parties other than those third parties such as banks, processing gateways and merchant processors required to process your purchase, and you understand that we cannot control how the banks, processing gateways or merchant processors will use such personal financial information. Therefore, you hereby consent to such sharing of personal financial information. You agree to assume the risk and agree that it is your responsibility to properly handle, secure, not store and destroy such personal financial information as may be necessary to protect it from misuse. You hereby consent to such sharing of personal financial information and hold us harmless and indemnify us from any claims, breaches, loss, or damage resulting from the use of those banks, processing gateways, payment facilitators, and merchant processors we use. You agree we shall not be liable to you or any third party for misuse of such content or personal financial information.

We may disclose information we collect from you to an affiliate or other third party in the event of any merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, reorganization, liquidation, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets, or stock.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website or use our Services. These third-party advertising companies may use advertising technologies such as cookies, web beacons and other similar advertising technologies. These companies may use aggregated information about your visits to our website or use of our Services and third party sites in order to provide advertisements and promotions about our Services that we believe users may find of interest.

We may also release user information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our Terms and Policy, or protect ours or other's rights, property, or safety. However, non- personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for data analysis, improving our Services, marketing, promotional, advertising, or other uses.

**Online eCommerce Platform**

We may use an online e-commerce platform that allows us to provide the Services and make them available to you. Your information, including personal information, may be transmitted through, and stored on third-party servers in an encrypted format. We do not store your personal financial information and it is not processed on our servers. By using our Services you consent to our collection, disclosure, storage, and use of your personal information in accordance with this Policy and our Terms o. You hereby consent to such sharing of personal financial information and hold us harmless and indemnify us from any claims, breaches, loss, or damage resulting from the use of the ecommerce platforms we use. You agree to assume the risk and agrees that it is their responsibility to properly handle, secure, not store and destroy such personal financial information as may be necessary to protect it from misuse. You agree that we are not liable to you for misuse of such content or personal financial information.

**Social Media, Posts, Texts, Forums and Profiles**

You agree that we may make available through our website, third party sites or our Services certain forms of media either now existing or to be created in the future (for example, social media, message boards, chat functionality, videos, pictures, images, profile pages, text messaging and blogs) to which users may be able to post information. Please note that any information users provide on these various forms of media may become public and may be available to anyone who visits our website, third party sites, and to the general public, including without limitation ratings and reviews. We urge you to exercise discretion and good manners when providing information of any type or kind and deciding to disclose any personal information.

YOU AGREE THAT WE SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY LOSS CAUSED BY THE USE BY US OR ANY UNAUTHORIZED PERSON OR ENTITY OF ANY INFORMATION THAT USERS DISCLOSE THROUGH OUR WEBSITE, THIRD PARTY SITES OR THE USE OF THE SERVICES.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users may make any changes to their information at any time by logging into their account and changing their information. We will not distribute their personal information to outside parties without their consent. We will not distribute their personal information to outside parties without their consent, unless permitted by the Terms or this Policy.

**Security Not Guaranteed**

We use reasonable organizational, technical, and administrative measures to protect each user's personal information under our control. However, we cannot guarantee 100% percent protection and security of such personal information. Please do not email or text us credit card information and/or other sensitive information.

**Contact Us**

Please email us at legal@nextadmit.com if you would like to request that Your personal information be removed from our database.

4\. What we Don't do with the Information we Gather.

We will not disclose, sell, distribute, rent, lease or use any of your data or pass on any such personal information to third parties, which are not our officers, directors, members, managing members, employees, business partners, affiliates, strategic partners, licensors, licensees, independent contractors, third party service providers, agents or representatives, unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

We do not store your credit card information. The credit card information and actual processing does not take place on and is not stored on our servers. The transaction is processed on the servers of the particular credit card processor we use to process the transaction.

5\. Disclosure of Information.

1. **Third Party Service Providers.** We employ other companies and people as third party service providers to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. For example, we use a payment processing company to receive and process your credit card transactions for us. They do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us.
    
2. **Other Users.** Please note that if you submit any of your personally identifiable information to a portion of the Services that is accessible by other users, including an online forum or comment section, other Users will be able to see that personally identifiable information. Accordingly, only include information in such submissions that you are comfortable sharing with third parties.
    
3. **De-Identifiable Information.** We may de-identify your personally identifiable information so that you are not identified as an individual, and provide that information to our partners. We may also provide aggregate usage information to our partners (or allow partners to collect that information from you), who may use such information to understand how often and in what ways people use our Services, so that they, too, can provide you with an optimal online experience. However, we never disclose aggregate usage or de-identified information to a partner (or allow a partner to collect such information) in a manner that would identify you as an individual person.
    
4. **Business Transfers.** We may choose to buy or sell assets, and may share and/or transfer customer information in connection with the evaluation of and entry into such transactions. Also, if we (or our assets) are acquired, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through some other change of control, personally identifiable information could be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party.
    
5. **Legal Compliance.** We reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information that we believe is necessary to comply with law or court order; enforce or apply our [Terms](https://nextadmit.com/terms-of-service) and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Next Admit, our employees, our users, or others.

6\. Disclosure of Information.

We endeavor to protect the privacy of your account and other personally identifiable information we hold in our records, but unfortunately, we cannot guarantee complete security. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time and you agree to hold us harmless and indemnify us from such damages or losses you may incur as a result of such problems.

7\. Modification / Deletion of Information.

Through your account settings, you may access, and, in some cases, edit or delete the following information you've provided to us:

* name and password
* email address
* profile information, including scholastic information and College Application data you have uploaded to the site.

The information you can view, update, and delete may change as the Services change. If you have any questions about viewing or updating information we have on file about you, please contact us at legal@nextadmit.com.

Finally, if you request, we will remove your name and all other personally identifiable information that you have provided from the Services. Please understand, however, that it may be impossible to delete this information completely, due to backups and records of deletions. In addition, please understand that, if you request removal of your information, you will be unable to utilize associated features of the Services. You may not request the removal of de-identified, anonymous, or aggregate data from our databases.

8\. Age of Users.

Children under the age of 13 are not permitted to use, access or register for the Services in any way. We do not knowingly collect or solicit information from anyone under the age of 13. If we find out we have unknowingly collected personally identifiable information about a child under 13, we will take all reasonable measures to delete that information from our system as soon as possible.

9\. Changes to Policy.

We're constantly trying to improve our Services, so we may need to change this Policy from time to time as well, but we will alert you to changes by placing a notice on our website, by sending you an email, and/or by some other means. Please note that if you've opted not to receive notice emails from us (or you haven't provided us with your email address), those legal notices will still govern your use of the Services, and you are still responsible for reading and understanding them. If you use the Services after any changes to the Policy have been posted, that means you agree to all of the changes. Use of information we collect is subject to the Policy in effect at the time the information is used.

10\. Contact Us

If you have any questions about the Policy, the collection and sharing practices of our Services, or your use of the Services, please contact us at legal@nextadmit.com.
